[
  {
    "question": "What coding language is used in making the structure of a website?",
    "info": "Think about the 3 main coding languages",
    "answer": "HTML"
  },

  {
    "question": "What coding language is used in styling the website?",
    "info": "Think about the 3 main coding languages",
    "answer": "CSS"
  },

  {
    "question": "What coding language is used to make buttons function in a website?",
    "info": "Think about the 3 main coding languages",
    "answer": "Javascript"
  },

  {
    "question": "What are objects like text, images etc. called in HTML?",
    "info": "Think about <h1>",
    "answer": "Tag"
  },
  
  {
    "question": "Which word does a website use to identify CSS?",
    "info": "Think about how you write CSS in a HTML file",
    "answer": "style"
  },
  
  {
    "question": "Which word does a website use to identify Javascript?",
    "info": "Think about how you write Javascript in a HTML file",
    "answer": "script"
  },
  
  {
    "question": "What can be attached to connections?",
    "info": "Think about changing the color of a button",
    "answer": "Functions"
  },
  
  {
    "question": "What does CSS require in order to work?",
    "info": "Think about where you write tags",
    "answer": "HTML"
  },

  {
    "question": "What are classes and id's called in CSS?",
    "info": "Think about '.' and '#'",
    "answer": "Selectors"
  },
  
  {
    "question": "Where can you learn more about HTML, CSS and Javascript?",
    "info": "Think about the 'Learn more' website",
    "answer": "W3Schools"
  }
  
]
